Jared Stefanowicz

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER & STUDENT

jaredStef@icloud.com (570) 472-5303 jaredStef.me Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

Profile

I'm a freelance iOS developer, entrepreneur, and student. I launched my first app as a sophomore in high school and have served many happy clients helping make their iOS app ideas a reality. I am interested in fintech and quantitative finance

Experience

Founder & Freelance iOS Developer Appitech LLC

Apr 2016 - Present

Worked with multiple clients from start to finish making their app ideas a reality. Gained experience building client relations, managing expectations, price negotiations, and developing high quality, mission critical work in a time conscious manner

Intern CoalCreative.com

Jul 2017 - Nov 2017 Wilkes Barre, PA Created websites using WordPress, HTML, and CSS. Attended meetings with clients and communicated progress updates on tasked projects

Volunteering

Judge, Speaker OwlHacks April, 2019

Ambassador Student Voice

Aug 2017 - May 2018

Attended monthly meetings, wrote op-eds and guides, circulated petitions, spoke to school board at public meetings

Junior Leadership Program Graduate Leadership Wilkes-Barre

Sep 2016 - May 2017

Planned and held charity event raising ~\$2k for nonprofit Victory Sport. Spoke to newspapers and generated interest through social media ad campaigns while tasked as group treasurer and in charge of outreach

Licenses & Certifications

Bloomberg Market Concepts Bloomberg LP - Nov. 2018

Education

Bachelor Business Administration Finance (Asset Pricing) | Minor: Mathematics

Fox School of Business at Temple University Fall 2018 - Spring 2022 (expected)

GPA: 3.93, Dean's List

Temple Economic Society (TES), Entrepreneurial Students Association (ESA), Johnson & Hardwick Residence Hall Community Council Vice President, Intramural Floor Hockey

HS Diploma

Hanover Area Jr/Sr High School 2014 - 2018 President Business Club, Senior Class Treasurer, Design Editor Yearbook, Voted most likely to succeed

Courses

Creativity and Organizational Innovation

Data Science

Awards

2nd - Vanguard ETF Trading Challenge Temple University April, 2019

National Competitor - Securities & Investments **FBLA**

2.018

1st Place - Computer Fair Programming Category LIU 18 2017, 2016

National Competitor - Intro. to Info. Technology **FBLA**

2016

1st Place Congressional App Challenge PA District 11 Feb. 2016

Skills

Python

iOS Development (Swift / Obj. C)

